affordabletours.com 2010-12-31

# Privacy Policy - Huge Discounts on: Tours, Globus Tours, Trafalgar Tours, Cosmos Tours, Collette, Contiki, Insight, General, CIE and More.

Protecting Your Privacy

This Privacy Policy is part of our terms and conditions. This privacy policy applies to the website AffordableTours.com and its parent company Castles of the World, Inc. This privacy policy informs users of how we collect, store and manage data that is gathered on our website about our users.

Information of a non-personal nature

Our website actively logs and records information of a non-personal nature such a referral websites, visits, length of sessions, domains and more. We aggregate and use this non-personal data to improve our website experience for clients. We also record the IP address of the computers that visit our website. This information allows us to serve our clients better.

How We Use Your Information

You are not required to submit personal information to use our website. Our website will not automatically record any information about users which is readily personally identifiable. However, you may submit your personal information to us by several means on our website and through the telephone and email. Any information that you voluntarily submit may be used by us to provide you with enhanced services such as providing you with products and services that you may have requested. We have the utmost respect for your privacy and security. We may collect information that you supply in order to provide a more personalized experience and to alert you of offers and services which closely match your interests. Your privacy is important to us. Any information that we collect online or via the telephone is done to provide you with the best website experience and service possible.

We may also share your information with legal authorities in response to subpoenas, to respond to court orders and other legal processes; and to exercise our legal rights as may be required by the law. We reserve the right to use all information for such legal purposes.

Business Partners

We may share your data with certain business partners and vendors in order to provide you with enhanced services such a mailing you brochures and promotional emails. We use the utmost care and respect for your privacy when selecting such business partners in order to protect your privacy. We require from our business partners that they ensure that the data we provide them will not be transferred to any other third parties for any uses not authorized by us. 

Information given to suppliers by us

In order for us to provide your vacation services we may be required by our suppliers to provide your personal information to them. In such cases we strive to provide as little information as may be necessary. Our suppliers, such as the tour operators and cruise lines that will eventually provide the travel services we offer on this website, will use that data to help provide you with travel services that you may have purchased. For example, such services include the mailing of travel documents and related materials to you. We do not control how that data is used by our suppliers after that point. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any particular supplier you choose to travel with in order to determine how this data may be used.

Changes to Our Privacy Policy

AffordableTours.com and its parent company reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Statement at any time and for any reason. If there are material changes to this statement or in how we will use your personal information, we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. Please check back periodically to learn of any changes in ways in which we may use this data.

Agreement of Use

By using our Site you are indicating that you have read and accepted the information practices in our Privacy Policy.

Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Third party advertisements and use of cookies

AffordableTours.com uses third party vendors and these providers show our ads across different sites on the internet. Our third party vendors include Google, Yahoo, MSN and others. Our ads appear on networks across the internet from these and other providers. Some of these third party vendors including Google use cookies to deliver you ads based on any previous visits you may have made to our website. You may opt-out of the use of Google cookies by visiting the [Google ads opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

If you have further questions regarding this policy and its use you may contact us at:  

AffordableTours.com  
11150 Cash RD  
Stafford, TX 77477
